onthecity.org 2016-06-20

# Privacy & Security Policy | ACS Technologies

Date Last Revised: 07/15/2014

## Privacy & Security Policy

ACS Technologies Group, Inc. ("ACST") is committed to protecting the privacy of our clients and the security of their data, especially those who access ACST sites (including without limitation acstechnologies.com, onrealm.org, onthecity.org, etc (Individually and collectively, the Sites) and corresponding services (the Sites and services are collectively referred to as the “Services”). This Privacy and Security Policy is designed to inform you about the types of information that we gather about you and your organization, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of that information. “You” and “your” as used herein refers to the individual, or an entity bound by an individual authorized to act on behalf of the entity, desiring to use the Sites and/or ACST software (“ACST Software”) and to be bound by this Privacy and Security Policy and ACST’s Terms of Use and Service.

### Collection and Use of Your Personal Information

For all visitors to its Sites, ACST collects general data pertaining to each website visitor, such as the visitor's IP address, operating system, browser type and version number, and the web pages viewed. This information is aggregated with all other visitor information.

ACST collects personal information, which means information by which specific individuals can be identified, including name, identification number, mailing address, e-mail address, and other personal characteristics or attributes. ACST will process personal information collected from you fairly and lawfully and will not use such personal information for purposes that are incompatible with the purposes it was requested and received. For example, ACST will use your personal information to process orders; to help us to improve our Sites and ACST Software and your online experience; to provide you with information about our products and services; for ordering, customer support, payment, processing and service purposes; to transact business with us; for credit checks, collections and related billing or credit purposes; and as otherwise allowed by law.

In addition to personal information you provide to us for the purpose of ordering products, you may provide financial information to us for the purpose of extending credit to you and/or selling products and services to you. This data is only used to process financial transactions and evaluate your credit worthiness, and is reviewed periodically as long as your account is active. It is shared with financial institutions as a normal course of doing business. Your account status and payment history is also reported to various credit reporting agencies.

### Sharing Your Personal Information

ACST may share your personal information within our organization, with any ACST subsidiary worldwide, or with authorized third parties (e.g., business partners, suppliers and financial institutions) as described in this policy. We may also disclose information in response to subpoenas, governmental requests or other legal process or to otherwise protect our legal or contractual obligations. We will not sell or otherwise transfer your personal information to individuals or entities outside of us or one of our authorized partners or resellers without your approval.

### Cookies

A cookie is a type of identifier sent from a website to your computer system via your web browser to provide tailored features. ACST uses cookies in order to secure and confirm your information when logging into partner access with your private login name and password. We do not use this information for any other purpose than to grant you access to secured specific reseller only website pages. 

### E-mail Communications

ACST may provide customers with promotional announcements for savings, rebates, product-related information, product updates, and product launches. These announcements can be stopped at any time by selecting the opt-out feature at the bottom of the e-mail; provided, however, this opt-out does not apply to non-promotional information provided to customers regarding their accounts or purchased product or services. We do not sell these e-mail lists to any of our business partners for any reason.

### Third Party Service: Promotions, Events and Webinars

From time to time, ACST may collect personal information for promotions, events and webinars. This information may be disclosed to our third-party partners for the limited purpose of awarding prizes and/or developing business opportunities.

### Blogs and other Forums

If you use a communication platform for content creation, sharing, or distribution on any of our Sites or using ACST Software, you should be aware that any information you submit there can be read, collected or used by other users and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these forums. These forums may be hosted by ACST, by our customers and/or by one of our third party service providers on ACST's behalf. ACST is not responsible, or liable to any customer or third party, for the substance or accuracy of any information or material posted by you or any other user of the ACTS Sites, ACST Software or communication platforms.

### Communication Preferences and Reviewing Your Personal Information

You can manage your communication preferences by contacting us at acstechnologies.com or sending a letter to the mailing address below. When contacting us please include your name, e-mail address, and the details of your request. For example, if you wish to unsubscribe from a newsletter, include the name of the newsletter. You can also access and update your personal information by contacting us at acstechnologies.com or sending a letter to the mailing address below that includes you name, e-mail address, account ID and the purpose of the request.

### Security of Your Personal Information

ACST operates secure data networks protected by industry standard security measures to protect your personal information from loss and misuse including, without limitation, firewalls, encryption, and password protection systems. ACST’s security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary.

### Disclosure of your information to protect our rights or if required by law

Notwithstanding the foregoing, ACST reserves the right (and you authorize ACST) to share or disclose your personal information when ACST determines, in its sole discretion, that the disclosure of such information is necessary or appropriate:

  * To enforce our rights against you or in connection with a breach by you of this Privacy and Security Policy or the acstechnologies.com Terms of Use;
  * To prevent prohibited or illegal activities; or
  * When required by any applicable law, rule regulation, subpoena or other legal process.

### Data may be transferred upon change of control

Personal information may be transferred to a third party as a result of a sale, acquisition, merger, reorganization or other change of control. If we sell, merge or transfer any part of our business, part of the sale may include your personal information. If so, you will be asked if you'd like to stop receiving promotional information following any change of control. 

### Transport or deletion of data

Your data belongs to you. You can remove it anytime you want and you should remove it just prior to requesting us to delete your account. When you request us to stop using the Sites or ACST Software, your data may be permanently expunged from our primary production servers and further access to your account may not be possible. We will also promptly disconnect any connection we had established to your account information and delete all account credentials. However, portions of your data, consisting of aggregate data derived from your account information, may remain on our production servers indefinitely. Your data may also remain on a backup server or media. ACST keeps these backups to ensure our continued ability to provide services to you in the event of malfunction or damage to our primary production servers. We also reserve the right to use any aggregated or anonymous data derived from or incorporating your personal information. If you have special requirements, please send ACST a written request for consideration, and ACST may be able to accommodate your needs for an additional charge.

### Children's Privacy

In accordance with ACST’s Terms of Use and Service, we cannot prohibit minors from visiting ACST sites. We must rely on parents, guardians and those responsible for supervising children under 13 to decide which materials are appropriate for such children to view, participate, upload to the Sites, and/or purchase. We require that all usage of the Sites be made by individuals 13 years of age or older. EACH TIME YOU USE ONE OR MORE OF THE SITES, YOU ARE REPRESENTING TO ACST AND THE SITES THAT YOU ARE AN INDIVIDUAL 13 YEARS OF AGE OR OLDER. If it becomes necessary to collect the personal information of children under the age of 13, we must receive verifiable parental consent prior to collection. If we learn that we have collected children's personal information without parental consent, we will delete it from our systems.

### Maintaining of confidentiality of Login ID and Password

We maintain strict rules to help prevent others from guessing your password. We also recommend that you change your password periodically. Your password must be 6-16 characters in length. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your Login ID and Password. You may not provide these credentials to any third party. If you believe that they have been stolen or been made known to others, you must contact us immediately at acstechnologies.com, but in any event you should change your password immediately. We are not responsible if someone else accesses your account through information they have obtained from you or through a violation by you of this Privacy and Security Policy or the ACST Terms of Use and Service.

### Governing Law

This Privacy and Security Policy and your rights and ACST’s responsibilities hereunder are governed by the laws of the State of South Carolina. In the event of any dispute involving this Privacy and Security Policy, you agree to submit to personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the state and federal courts located in Florence County, South Carolina.

### Updates to Privacy and Security Policy

We update this Privacy and Security Policy periodically. The date last revised appears at the top of the Policy. Changes take effect immediately upon posting.

### How to Contact Us

You can contact ACST by contacting us at acstechnologies.com or by sending a letter to the mailing address listed below. Please include your contact information, name of ACST web site or service, and a detailed description of your request or privacy concern. If a client, you may also contact us by phone by calling ACS Technologies Client Support at 1-800-669-2509.

**ACS Technologies Group, Inc.,** 180 Dunbarton Drive, Florence, SC 29501, United States
